timpaplr.com 2015-12-31

# Privacy Statement - Timpa PLR

Your privacy is important to me. To better protect your privacy I provide this notice explaining my online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, I make it available on my homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

Some Third Party ad servers or ad networks may use cookies to track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies, timpaplr.com has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers.

**Material Connection Disclosure**  
You should assume that this website has an affiliate relationship with the providers of goods and services mentioned on this site and may be compensated when you purchase. You should always perform due diligence before buying goods or services from anyone via the Internet or offline.

**Collection of Personal Information**  
When visiting timpaplr.com, the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Links to third party Websites**  
I may include links on this site for your use and reference. I’m not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from my own.

**Changes to this Privacy Statement**  
The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at my discretion.

If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of timpaplr.com then you may **[contact me](http://timpaplr.com/contact/ "Contact Form").**
